( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Don't do this!
لا تفعل هذا!
I'm going to write my next story.
سأكتب قصتي التالية.
And, I hope
وآمل ذلك
that you won't be in it.
أنك لن تكون مشاركاً فيه.
[Ding]
[دينغ]
Since you're not willing to wake up,
بما أنك غير راغب في الاستيقاظ،
I shall keep you company in your dreams.
سأرافقك في أحلامك.
Is this...
هذا هو...
where Xie Xinxu used to live?
أين كان يعيش شي شينشو؟
Why am I dreaming about him again?
لماذا أحلم به مجدداً؟
♪I am lost in the dizzy pull of your fierce attraction♪
♪أنا تائه في سحر جاذبيتك القوية التي تُدوّخني♪
♪So devoted that I would let this obsession last until the end of my life♪
♪مخلصٌ لدرجة أنني سأدع هذا الهوس يستمر حتى نهاية حياتي♪
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
I only killed your parents because I went berserk.
لم أقتل والديك إلا لأنني فقدت صوابي.
If you kill me, you'll die too!
إذا قتلتني، ستموت أنت أيضاً!
I only desire your death.
لا أرغب إلا في موتك.
Am I dreaming about Xie Xinxu avenging his parents?
هل أحلم بأن شي شينشو ينتقم لوالديه؟
What else is he up to?
ماذا يفعل أيضاً؟
♪The touch of your warm embrace♪
♪لمسة حضنك الدافئ♪
♪I'm a slave to you♪
أنا عبدٌ لك
♪Can you feel that you're my fire?♪
♪هل تشعر أنك ناري؟♪
He's still playing the victim even in my dream?
هل ما زال يلعب دور الضحية حتى في حلمي؟
I should leave this dream
يجب أن أترك هذا الحلم
and create the next.
ثم ابتكر التالي.
You're misbehaving again.
أنت تتصرف بشكل سيء مرة أخرى.
♪I'm warning, warning you♪
♪أحذرك، أحذرك♪
♪So put your loving hand out darling…♪
♪مدّي يدكِ الحنونة يا عزيزتي…♪
Siyuan?
سيوان؟
Siyuan!
سيوان!
Siyuan...
سيوان...
♪I am lost in the dizzy pull of your fierce attraction♪
♪أنا تائه في سحر جاذبيتك القوية التي تُدوّخني♪
♪So devoted that I would let this obsession last until the end of my life♪
♪مخلصٌ لدرجة أنني سأدع هذا الهوس يستمر حتى نهاية حياتي♪
♪Will your love ever burn as fiercely as mine?♪
هل سيشتعل حبك يوماً ما بنفس شدة حبي؟
I think...
أظن...
I think I understand why I'm having this dream.
أعتقد أنني أفهم سبب رؤيتي لهذا الحلم.
Xie Xinxu, that's enough!
شي شينشو، هذا يكفي!
Look closely.
انظر جيداً.
Look at the person you keep trying to kill.
انظر إلى الشخص الذي تحاول قتله باستمرار.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
So, this is the inner world
إذن، هذا هو العالم الداخلي
of a person who's living in
لشخص يعيش في
a world full of hatred, grudges, and vengeance.
عالم مليء بالكراهية والأحقاد والانتقام.
No matter if it's the culprit who murdered your parents
بغض النظر عما إذا كان هو الجاني الذي قتل والديك
or Siyuan,
أو سيوان،
who trained you brutally,
من قام بتدريبك بوحشية؟
with every stab you take at them,
مع كل طعنة توجهها إليهم،
you end up stabbing yourself in the end.
ينتهي بك الأمر بطعن نفسك في النهاية.
This version of you is terrifying.
هذه النسخة منك مرعبة.
Pitiful, too.
مثير للشفقة أيضاً.
However,
لكن،
thanks to that, I've realized
بفضل ذلك، أدركت
that if this is what awaits at the end of vengeance,
إذا كان هذا ما ينتظرنا في نهاية المطاف بعد الانتقام،
I shall stop hating you
سأتوقف عن كرهك
and tormenting you.
وتعذيبك.
Because in the end,
لأنه في النهاية،
it'll trap me in an everlasting nightmare as well.
سيوقعني ذلك في كابوس أبدي أيضاً.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Let's stop dwelling on this world.
دعونا نتوقف عن التفكير في هذا العالم.
We're all worn out from the fuss.
لقد أنهكنا جميعاً من هذه الضجة.
Why don't we just give each other a break?
لماذا لا نمنح بعضنا البعض استراحة؟
Fine.
بخير.
Did you form a pact with me with this blood exchanging device?
هل أبرمت معي اتفاقاً بخصوص جهاز تبادل الدم هذا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
As for the things that aren't essential,
أما بالنسبة للأشياء غير الضرورية،
I'll mail them to you later.
سأرسلها إليك بالبريد لاحقاً.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
there's something you have the right to know.
هناك شيء يحق لك معرفته.
Regarding my parents' death,
بخصوص وفاة والديّ،
Siyuan didn't do it.
لم يفعلها سيوان.
My parents were killed by a Ren
قُتل والداي على يد رين
by accident.
عن طريق الصدفة.
Therefore,
لذلك،
Siyuan merely followed Xia Shang's orders.
لم يفعل سيوان سوى تنفيذ أوامر شيا شانغ.
He wasn't the mastermind.
لم يكن هو العقل المدبر.
It's good to have a conclusion.
من الجيد التوصل إلى خاتمة.
This way,
من هنا،
at least there'd be less bad blood between us.
على الأقل ستكون هناك ضغائن أقل بيننا.
And, you can be more relaxed.
ويمكنك أن تكون أكثر استرخاءً.
Do you intend to expose Xia Shang for her crimes?
هل تنوين فضح شيا شانغ بسبب جرائمها؟
I plan
أخطط
to gather more evidence
لجمع المزيد من الأدلة
so that she won't get a chance to make a comeback.
حتى لا تحصل على فرصة للعودة.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
What do you plan to do?
ما الذي تنوي القيام به؟
Pursue my PhD
متابعة دراسة الدكتوراه
and develop a drug to eliminate the virus.
وتطوير دواء للقضاء على الفيروس.
But first,
لكن أولاً،
I need to find the last fragment.
أحتاج إلى إيجاد الجزء الأخير.
It seems
يبدو
we still have some sort of chemistry.
لا يزال بيننا نوع من التوافق.
You get hooked on papers the moment you read them,
تُصبح مُدمناً على قراءة الصحف بمجرد أن تبدأ في قراءتها،
pulling all-nighters here and there.
السهر طوال الليل هنا وهناك.
I've got these liver-protecting tablets for you.
لدي هذه الأقراص الواقية للكبد من أجلك.
Remember to take them.
تذكر أن تأخذها معك.
I've also prepared Vitamin C,
لقد قمت أيضاً بتحضير فيتامين سي،
lutein,
اللوتين،
and stomach medicine for you.
ودواء للمعدة لك.
Eating too much takeout can easily cause stomachaches.
الإفراط في تناول الوجبات الجاهزة قد يسبب آلاماً في المعدة بسهولة.
These can be used for emergencies.
يمكن استخدامها في حالات الطوارئ.
And this.
وهذا أيضاً.
This is a new drug developed by Mr. Ding.
هذا دواء جديد طوره السيد دينغ.
It can delay the onset of viral outbreaks
يمكن أن يؤخر ذلك ظهور تفشي الفيروسات
in your body to some extent.
في جسمك إلى حد ما.
Take one shot every month.
خذ جرعة واحدة كل شهر.
But if you feel unwell,
لكن إذا شعرت بتوعك،
you must contact me.
يجب عليك الاتصال بي.
Rest early.
استرح مبكراً.
If this is our last night together,
إذا كانت هذه ليلتنا الأخيرة معاً،
it shouldn't hurt
لا ينبغي أن يكون مؤلماً
to indulge a bit, right?
لنستمتع قليلاً، أليس كذلك؟
There's something I want to know.
هناك شيء أريد أن أعرفه.
If you have to rate how much you hate me
إذا كان عليك تقييم مدى كرهك لي
on a scale of 1 to 10,
على مقياس من 1 إلى 10،
how much would you rate it?
ما هو تقييمك له؟
Ten.
عشرة.
But I also love you
لكنني أحبك أيضاً
to the same extent.
وبنفس القدر.
I truly,
أنا حقاً،
truly,
حقا،
truly love you.
أحبك حقاً.
We have the ultimate love-hate relationship.
لدينا علاقة حب وكراهية مثالية.
We all need time to see clearly
جميعنا نحتاج إلى وقت لنرى بوضوح
whether it's the beautiful memories or the painful feelings
سواء كانت ذكريات جميلة أو مشاعر مؤلمة
that carry us further.
وهذا ما يدفعنا إلى الأمام.
I thought you would sentence
ظننت أنك ستصدر حكماً.
our relationship
علاقتنا
to death.
حتى الموت.
Thank you
شكرًا لك
for the suspended sentence.
فيما يتعلق بالحكم الموقوف التنفيذ.
Look at how messy your hair is.
انظري إلى مدى فوضوية شعرك.
If so, let's cherish the last few hours
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، فلنستمتع بالساعات القليلة الأخيرة
that we'll spend together.
سنقضيها معاً.
For example?
على سبيل المثال؟
For example...
على سبيل المثال...
♪Sky opens wide♪
♪السماء تنفتح على مصراعيها♪
♪You close your eyes♪
♪تغمض عينيك♪
♪No one can find you♪
♪لا أحد يستطيع العثور عليك♪
♪But still it begins♪
♪لكنها لا تزال تبدأ♪
♪And so it is♪
♪وهكذا يكون الأمر♪
♪Your eyes can't hide you♪
♪لا تستطيع عيناك إخفاءك♪
♪You build those castles in the sand♪
♪تبني تلك القصور على الرمال♪
♪And hope with everything you have♪
♪وأمل بكل ما أوتيت من قوة♪
♪The wind is calm tonight♪
♪الريح هادئة الليلة♪
[Wu Nongyu PhD Student]
[وو نونجيو طالب دكتوراه]
Nongyu.
نونجيو.
We're done with work.
انتهينا من العمل.
Do you want to join us for a meal?
هل ترغب بالانضمام إلينا لتناول وجبة؟
It's our treat.
إنها ضيافتنا.
I was away on a business trip
كنت مسافراً في رحلة عمل
when you first joined us six months ago.
عندما انضممت إلينا لأول مرة قبل ستة أشهر.
It's been six months,
لقد مرّت ستة أشهر،
and I haven't had the chance to hold a welcoming feast for you.
ولم تتح لي الفرصة لإقامة وليمة ترحيبية لكم.
Just do me a favor
أرجوك، افعل لي معروفاً.
and join us for a meal, okay?
وانضم إلينا لتناول وجبة، حسناً؟
Sorry about that.
أعتذر عن ذلك.
My boyfriend is here to pick me up.
حبيبي هنا ليصطحبني.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪